Guide to the Stanford University Theater Scrapbooks
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University Theater Scrapbooks
1934-1961
SC0698
Stanford University. Department of Drama.
18 Linear feet (27 boxes)
The scrapbooks contain clippings and programs, with some calendars, articles, and other printed matter. The primary subject is theatrical presentations at Stanford and in Palo Alto, with lesser coverage of other cultural events (concerts, lectures, debates, etc.)
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use.
Description of the Collection
The scrapbooks in Series 1, dated 1934-1961, contain clippings and programs with some calendars, articles, and other printed matter. The primary subject is theatrical presentations at Stanford and in Palo Alto, with lesser coverage of other cultural events (concerts, lectures, debates, etc.) The scrapbooks in Series 2 contain clippings and programs, 1942-1947, covering all types of cultural events at Stanford, including theater, concerts, and lectures.
Arrangement note
The scrapbooks are arranged chronologically within each series.
Access Terms
College and school drama; Performing arts--California; Scrapbooks
Collection Contents
- Scrapbooks, 1934-1961; Series 1
  - 1934-1935 (Box 1)
  - 1935-1936 (Box 1)
  - 1937 (Box 1)
  - 1936-1937 (Box 2)
  - 1937-1938 (Box 2)
  - 1937-1938 (Box 2)
  - 1938 Jan-1939 Nov (Box 3)
  - 1939 spring-summer (Box 3)
  - 1938 Apr-Aug (Box 3)
  - 1938 summer-Nov (Box 4)
  - 1938 Aug-1939 Jan (Box 4)
  - 1938 Nov-1939 Mar (Box 4)
  - 1939 Jan-May (Box 4)
  - 1939 Mar-Jul (Box 5)
  - 1939 May-Aug (Box 5)
  - 1939 Jul-Nov (Box 5)
  - 1939 (Box 6)
  - 1939 (Box 6)
  - 1940 (Box 6)
  - 1940 (Box 7)
  - 1940 (Box 7)
  - 1940 (Box 7)
  - 1941 (Box 8)
  - 1941 (Box 8)
  - 1941 Jul-Sep (Box 8)
  - 1941 Jun-Aug (Box 9)
  - 1942 Jan-Jul (Box 9)
  - 1941 Sep-1942 Feb (Box 9)
  - 1942 Jul-Nov (Box 10)
  - 1942 Feb-May (Box 10)
  - 1943 Apr-Dec (Box 10)
  - 1943 Dec-1944 Oct (Box 11)
  - 1945 (Box 11)
  - 1945 Jul-1946 Jan (Box 11)
  - 1946 Feb-Nov (Box 12)
  - 1946 Nov-1947 Apr (Box 12)
  - 1947 Apr-Sep (Box 12)
  - 1947 Oct-1948 Jan (Box 13)
  - 1948 Jan-May (Box 13)
  - 1948 Apr-Jul (Box 13)
  - 1948 Jul-Oct (Box 14)
  - 1948 Oct-1949 Feb (Box 14)
  - 1949 Feb-May (Box 14)
  - 1949 May-Jul (Box 15)
  - 1949 Jul-Aug (Box 15)
  - 1949 Aug-Dec (Box 15)
  - 1949 Dec-1950 Feb (Box 15)
  - 1950 Feb-May (Box 16)
  - 1950 May-Aug (Box 16)
  - 1950 Aug-1951 Jan (Box 16)
  - 1951 Jan-Apr (Box 16)
  - 1951 Apr-Jul (Box 17)
  - 1951 Jul-Oct (Box 17)
  - 1951 Oct-1952 Jan (Box 17)
  - 1952 Jan-Apr (Box 18)
  - 1952 Apr-Jul (Box 18)
  - 1952 Aug-1953 Jan (Box 18)
  - 1953 Jan-Mar (Box 18)
  - 1953 Mar-Jun (Box 19)
  - 1953 Jun-Oct (Box 19)
  - 1953 Oct-Dec (Box 19)
  - 1954 Jan-Mar (Box 19)
  - 1954 Mar-May (Box 20)
  - 1954 May-Oct (Box 20)
  - 1954 Sep-Dec (Box 20)
  - 1954 Dec-1955 Mar (Box 20)
  - 1955 Mar-May (Box 21)
  - 1955 May-Jul (Box 21)
  - 1955 Jul-Nov (Box 21)
  - 1955 Nov-1956 Feb (Box 21)
  - 1956 Feb-May (Box 22)
  - 1956 Apr-Aug (Box 22)
  - 1956 Aug-1957 May (Box 22)
  - 1957 May-Oct (Box 23)
  - 1957 Aug-1958 Mar (Box 23)
  - 1958 Mar-Oct (Box 23)
  - 1958 Oct-1959 Feb (Box 23)
  - 1959 Mar-Sep (Box 23)
  - 1959 Sep-1960 Feb (Box 23)
  - 1960 Feb-1961 Jan (Box 23)
  - 1961 Jan-Aug (Box 23)
- Additional scrapbooks, 1942-1947; Series 2
  - 1942 May 8-1944 Mar 9 (Box 1)
  - 1944 Mar 9-1945 Dec (Box 2)
  - 1946 Jan 18-1947 Oct 23 (Box 3)